<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Bobe's Thoughts - About Me</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/about-me.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2020-07-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>About Me</title><link href="/about-me.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-07-14T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Bobe Kryant</name></author><id>tag:None,2020-07-14:/about-me.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;!--- Modified: 2017-11-27 12:30 --&gt;

&lt;!--- Category: About &lt;br&gt; --&gt;

&lt;!--- Tags: Introduction, Misc --&gt;

&lt;!--- Authors: Bobe Kryant --&gt;

&lt;!--- Summary: What does your post talk about? Write here. --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing under this pseudonym in honor of my favorite athlete, someone who has inspired and motivated me throughout my life. This blog is a place for me to reason out some of my thoughts in a more coherent manner and to create timestamps for these ideas. The main …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;!--- Modified: 2017-11-27 12:30 --&gt;

&lt;!--- Category: About &lt;br&gt; --&gt;

&lt;!--- Tags: Introduction, Misc --&gt;

&lt;!--- Authors: Bobe Kryant --&gt;

&lt;!--- Summary: What does your post talk about? Write here. --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing under this pseudonym in honor of my favorite athlete, someone who has inspired and motivated me throughout my life. This blog is a place for me to reason out some of my thoughts in a more coherent manner and to create timestamps for these ideas. The main two topics will be finance and sports.
On the finance side, I will write about interesting investments in the traditional markets and in the crypto space. Regarding sports, most of the posts will focus around 
sports analytics and sports betting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been investing/trading for over a decade. In this blog, I want to focus on popular tailwinds and how they may benefit certain industries and players in the upcoming decade.
I have a particular interest in tech (more specifically SaaS) sector and will be looking at these companies closely. In addition, I have been around crypto since my college suite-mate introduced me to Litecoin mining. I will be posting my thoughts about the future of crypto, especially as it relates to the exchange and DeFi space.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Sports analytics and sports betting are still in the nascent stages. The legal sports betting handle is still a magnitude lower than the illegal sports betting handle, which leads to lower consolidated volume and higher vigs. Good clean data to do analytics is even harder to come by.
Unlike in finance, where many fin-tech companies entire business model revolve around cleaning and selling data, when dealing with sports the data is hard to come by. For instance, the NBA actively changes their api to prevent scraping. The pipeline requires the ability to web-scrape, store, and clean the data before any analysis can be done.
Nonetheless, I have built robust pipelines for the NBA, NFL, and UFC and I will share interesting insights and tidbits on each sport. I will try to open source as much code as possible so others can play around with data and code.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a statistics background and my day job is a quantitative researcher so my posts will probably lean on the quant side. I can be reached at bobekryant33824@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="About Me"></category></entry></feed>